Sorry, I thought nobody was here.
Didn't you realize you're in the wrong locker room?
General Dentistry Department
You sure aren't afraid to take on any patient.
Wear your glasses next time you go out.
Don't try to be a hero.
When you were saving that person earlier,
weren't your hands and eyes rock-steady?
How come now you can't even tell the locker rooms apart?
Need me to book you an eye appointment?
You have Anxiety Disorder.
I know.
Yesterday, I... I gave...
Don't say a word.
Pei Xi.
Come here, come here.
Coming.
Are we ready to begin?
Yes, we can begin.
Patient's Blood pressure 120/60.
Heart rate 56.
Vitals are stable. We're good.
Any Allergy history?
None.
Get ready for surgery.
Okay.
Boss, your surgery was amazing.
That was an eye-opener.
A full fifteen minutes faster than before.
Compared to last time,
you haven't improved much.
Dr. Jiang is still the best.
Junior, you still need practice.
Doctor, how's my son?
The surgery was a success.
President Fu, what did I tell you?
With Dr. Jiang here,
you can rest easy.
Yes.
Dr. Jiang, thank you so much.
Thank goodness you were here today.
Do you have time to grab a meal together?
It's settled then.
Vice President Qin, join us.
Doctor.
Thank you so much.
I...
Where's my daughter?
How is she?
Didn't you see her?
I'll go check.
Why are you hitting him?!
Dr. Jiang, are you okay?
Rich people's lives matter,
but my daughter's life is worthless?
Have you lost your mind?
Call the police, now!
Where's your conscience?
You knew my daughter's condition best.
My daughter got here before his son.
Why did you ignore my daughter
to operate on the rich man's son first?
Doctor.
I'm begging you.
She's my only daughter.
If you save my daughter,
I'll do anything you ask.
Doctor, save my daughter!
Save my daughter!
Sir.
What are you doing?
What do you think you're doing?
- Save my daughter! - Sir.
- Save my daughter! - This guy...
- Save my daughter! - Calm down first.
Let go!
Doctor.
I'm begging you.
Unscrupulous Doctor Assaults Patient's Family in Public
What is wrong with our society?
At Pingjin First Hospital,
Attending Physician Jiang Tiancai of the Oral and Maxillofacial Surgery Department,
during emergency patient care,
ignored the patient's needs.
Why have ERs become conflict hotspots?
Is it a lack of communication,
or the strain on medical resources?
Looking at recent events at Pingjin First Hospital...
Why did you hit him?
He's a patient's family member.
You're a doctor.
Do you see this?
The heart of a healer.
Why couldn't you just explain calmly?
If I told you
I didn't hit him,
would you believe me?
You...
Look, just look at this.
The video shows it clear as day.
And you're still making excuses?
You must
issue a public apology.
Explain why,
why you saved the rich man's kid first.
You...
Why?
Just for your national number one ranking,
you abandoned Grandma.
If you'd operated on Grandma first,
she wouldn't have died.
You killed her.
Faced with family and patients,
a doctor must make a choice.
Because life
never waits.
Maybe it's because
of my father's example.
Of course, you save the most valuable first.
I...
Since you hate him so much,
why did you choose to be just like him
and become a doctor?
Shouldn't you know that better than anyone?
Jiang Tiancai, listen to me.
I'm giving you two choices.
Either apologize publicly,
or be suspended.
The Golden Scalpel Award evaluations are about to start.
Don't you dare cause me trouble right now.
The Specialty Reputation Ranking is about to start.
I quit.